Her old eyes looked dimmer than ever.
Without saying anything, she tugged gently at his mane and led him round to
the end of the big barn, where the Seven Commandments were written.
>> [clears throat] >> For a minute or two, they stood gazing at the tarred wall with its white
lettering.
>> My sight is failing.
Even when I was young, I could not have read what was written there.
But it appears to me that that wall looks different.
Are the Seven Commandments the same as they used to be, Benjamin?
>> For once, Benjamin consented to break his rule, and he read out to her what
was written on the wall.
There was nothing there now except a single commandment.
It ran "All animals are equal, but some animals are more equal than others."
After that, it did not seem strange when, next day, the pigs who were
supervising the work of the farm all carried whips in their trotters.
It did not seem strange to learn that the pigs had bought themselves a
wireless set, were arranging to install a telephone, and had taken out
subscriptions to John Bull, Tit-Bits, and The Daily Mirror.
It did not seem strange when Napoleon was seen strolling in the farmhouse
garden with a pipe in his mouth.
No, not even when the pigs took Mr. Jones's clothes out of the wardrobes and put